我们都在这里
你上周死哪儿去了
给我他妈的说英语
Speak fucking English!
-他脸上的是什么  -天呐
- What's on his face? - Oh, my god!
天呐  天呐
Oh, my god, oh, my god!
他吸了我的可卡因
He got into my coke.
加拉格
Gallagher.
-他怎么样了  -他还活着
- How is he? - He's alive.
很可能留下永久性脑损伤
Could have permanent brain damage.
请你告诉他我爱他  好吗
Please tell me that I love him, okay?
我真的很抱歉
And I'm so, so sorry.
这不是菲奥娜的错
It wasn't Fiona's fault.
都没看到利亚姆  你知道的  对吧
Nobody saw Liam. You know that, right?
利亚姆住院了
Liam is in the hospital.
-他差点死了  -你昨晚上到哪儿去了
- And he almost died. - Where were you last night?
-马特家  -谁是马特
- Matt's. - Who's Matt?
你就是马特  那个传说中的马特吗
Oh, you're Matt? "The" Matt?
你他妈都多大了
How fucking old are you?
得先找到弗兰克
We got to find Frank,
不然利亚姆要被送去寄养家庭了
or they're gonna put Liam into foster care.
我操
Shit.
-弗兰克  -你差点死了
- Frank! - We almost lost you.
不会  我还没准备死呢
Nope. Not ready to punch my ticket yet.
加拉格
Gallagher...
你被保释了
You made bail.
我们只是来找兄弟的
We're just looking for our brother,
-伊恩·加拉格  -他上班去了
- Ian Gallagher. - He's at work.
白燕子俱乐部  在男孩城
The White Swallow, in Boystown.
几个军队宪兵正在找你
Some army M.P.S came by looking for you.
他们要以擅离职守罪逮捕你
They want to arrest you for going awol.
太可笑了
That's hilarious.
利亚姆
Liam.
-快让我看看  -小家伙
- Look at you. - Hey, buddy!
无耻家庭
第四季第七集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  扎克不渣   重案组李Sir   姚小事   君君
■
翻译：  青椒    爱卿遛小鸟    拉图    Greentie
时间轴：  加森   Kitty
■
校对：  Greentie
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
你能这样吗
Can you do this?
菲奥娜下来吃早餐了吗
Fiona coming down for breakfast?
她还没起来呢
She's not up yet.
喝菓珍咯  利亚姆
Here's your Tang, Liam.
给你  宝贝  快喝
Here you go, baby. Here.
要看着他喝完
Make sure he drinks the whole thing.
-他需要补充电解质  -好的
- He needs his electrolytes. - Okay.
就得这样  从现在起
That's right, and from now on,
除非是我们给你的
nothing goes in your mouth
否则你都别吃  小家伙
unless we give it to you, buddy.
-好的  -这是什么味儿
- Okay. - What's that smell?
还能是什么  弗兰克  不许再抽大麻了
Oh, guess. Frank, stop smoking weed!
卡尔  赶紧把利亚姆从楼梯口挪走
Ugh! Carl, get Liam away from the stairs.
听着  我今天会带利亚姆去学校
Look, I'll take Liam to school today.
顺便从那里弄点晚餐回来
I'll grab us some dinner while I'm there.
能弄到红酒烩鸡吗  希拉以前做过一次
What about co-co van? Sheila made it once.
那你就把那味道铭记于心吧
Yeah, well, I hope you remember what it tasted like.
因为这辈子你可能再没机会
It's probably the last time you're gonna have it
-尝到了  -我们可以叫个披萨
- in your life. - We could order a pizza.
菲奥娜以前加班的时候就会让我们叫
Fiona used to let us do that when she's working late.
不行  太贵了  知道吗
No, it's too expensive. All right?
咱们得重回购买三无产品
We're back to generics from Food 4 Less
和捡垃圾回收利用的生活了
and dumpster diving.
我可以买些日用品回来
I could buy a few groceries.
是吗  真是太好了
Yeah, that'd be nice
鉴于我们只是多了两张嘴要喂饱
since we have two extra mouths to feed.
你能不能去叫弗兰克别再抽大麻了
Now why don't you just tell Frank to lay off the weed?
他病得很厉害  比以前更严重
He's very sick. Worse than ever.
我们忙前忙后可不是为了
Yeah, well, we're very out on our asses
在社工意外到访时
if the social worker makes a surprise visit
发现屋子里到处都是大麻气味
and the place smells like Snoop Dogg.
就是  我们让你待在这里的
Yeah, the only reason we're letting you
唯一原因就是指望你能看好弗兰克
stay here is to take care of Frank.
我想你们还不了解状况
I don't think you guys understand.
-了解  -我们自打出娘胎以来
- Oh, understand? - We've lived with
就跟那个自恋的混蛋生活在一起了
that narcissistic asshole our whole lives.
你现在冒出来充大姐
Now you're trying to play big sis?
没赶你走算是你走运了
You're lucky we don't bounce you to the curb.
-就是  -所以我们说不准再抽大麻
- Yeah. - So if we say no more weed...
你就不能再让他抽大麻
we mean no more weed.
-好吧  -很好
- Okay. Fine. - Good.
各位都给我听好了
Now listen, everybody, remember
要是那个社工来了的话
that when the social worker does show up...
也包括你  恰奇  所以都听仔细了
And this includes you too, Chuckie, so listen up.
第一时间发短信给我  明白吗
You text me immediately. Okay?
-我会搭轻轨立马赶回来  -那菲奥娜呢
- I'll hop on the "L." - What about Fiona?
我已经接替她了  明白吗
I've got her covered, all right?
在我回来之前  你们想办法
I just need you to stall the social worker
拖住社工就行了
till I can get back.
-都听明白了吗  -是的
- Are we understood? - Yeah.
-明白吗  -明白
- Yes? - Yes.
我的车来了
Oh, that's my ride.
希拉出城这段时间我得去她家
Got to stop by Sheila's to water her plants
-给植物浇水  -小黛
- while she's out of town. - Deb.
我不回来吃晚饭了
And I won't be home for dinner.
为什么  你要去哪里
Why? Where you going?
去朋友家
Friends.
萨咪  听着
Hey, Sammi. Listen.
因为楼上的那个混球
We've been dumped into foster care
我们已经被送进寄养家庭太多次了
way too many times because of that prick upstairs.
我绝不会让它再次发生
There's no way I'm letting it happen again.
给你的
Here you go.
-早上好  -早上好
- Morning. - Morning
能让我搭个顺风车吗
Hey, can I get a ride?
你的顺风车  在那边
Your ride's...over there.
-别闹了  -别这样嘛  小维
- Mm-mm. Stop it. - Aw, come on, V.
不行  我肚子胀得难受还便秘
No. I'm too bloated and constipated.
-那让我帮你运动一下肠道  -真恶心
- I'll fuck it loose for you. - Ew!
我又不是说要开后庭
I don't mean in the butt.
清晨一炮  神清气爽
Morning sex keeps you regular.
不行  我没那心情
No, I'm not in the mood.
你总是说没心情
You're never in the mood.
还不是因为休伊  杜威和路易这三个娃
That's because Huey, Dewey, and Louie
名字来自唐老鸭的三胞胎外甥
把那里的空间都占满了
are taking up all the room down there.
在他们出生之前
Are we ever gonna have sex again
-咱们还能嘿咻吗  -应该没戏了
- before they come out? - Probably not.
搞不明白怎么会有女人说怀孕后性欲更强
Don't know how women say they get horny when they pregnant.
好吧  那你帮我撸出来
All right, well, jack me off then.
-你自己撸去  -好吧
- Jack yourself off. - Fine.
不过总得给我点东西看着吧
But let me get something to look at.
瞄一下你的咪咪
Peek at a titty.
我全身都毛茸茸的  恶心极了
Everything is hairy and gross.
什么时候的事  你没有毛呀
Since when? You're never hairy.
别碰我  都是荷尔蒙惹的祸
Leave me alone. From hormones.
我全身都在长毛
I got hair growing everywhere
还分泌黏液  都好几天了
and mucous coming out of me for days.
好吧
All right, fine.
我去浴室自己撸
I'm gonna go jack myself off in the bathroom.
不过想着你分泌黏液这件事
But I don't think it's gonna work
我应该是撸不出来了
thinking about all of your mucous.
我今天要借你的货车一用
I'm gonna need to borrow your truck today.
干嘛
What for?
我要载菲奥娜去法院参加预审
I've got to take Fiona to the courthouse for her prelim
之后还要去见马医生
and then I have a Dr. Ma appointment.
靠  不是吧  马医生
Oh, shit. No. Dr. Ma?
我要和你一起去
I gotta go with you.
我可不能错过超声波检查
I can't miss an ultrasound.
我要看着那些小家伙长大
I love watching those dudes grow,
但我今晚得上班
but I gotta work tonight.
是啊  你下周再陪我去吧
Yeah, well, you'll go next week.
好吧
All right.
记得带照片给我看
Bring me those pictures, okay?
你这就撸完了
You finished already?
了解自己嘛
Mm. Know myself.
干他妈啥
Hey, what the fuck?
给点隐私让我拉屎呗
Can I take a shit in private, please?
混蛋  找你男朋友去吧
Douche bag, go find your boyfriend.
滚出去  关门
Get the fuck out! Close the door.
我昨天找了他一天
I looked for him all day yesterday
他都不回我短信
and he's not answering my texts.
你说什么呢
What the fuck are you talking about?
别给我装傻
Don't play dumb with me.
伊恩
Ian!
因为你他才走的
You know, you're the reason that he left.
所以去找他
So go find him.
我得去工作了
I gotta go to work.
不关我的事
Not my fucking problem.
你知道吗
You know what?
什么都不关你的事
Nothing's ever your problem.
就一次  关心一下
For once, you know, make something your problem.
话说松鼠跟松饼有啥联系
The fuck does a squirrel have to do with waffles anyway?
操  曼迪
Ah, fuck. Mandy!
伙计  我们要出门  所以要把你的帽子
Hey, buddy, we're gonna leave the house, so we're gonna need
还有尿布装起来
your hat and diapers.
嗨  小宝贝
Hi, peanut.
没关系的
It's okay.
过来  过来  宝贝儿  过来
Come here. Come here, peanut. Come here.
你好些了吗
How are you? Huh?
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我永远不会伤害你
I would never do anything to hurt you.
这么可爱的小脸儿  我不会伤害你的
I would never do anything to hurt this face.
-真可爱  -利亚姆
- This face. - Hey, Liam.
好了  我们要迟到了
Come on. We're gonna be late.
-过来  伙计  -你要去哪
- Come here, bud. - Where you going?
学校
School.
-带利亚姆去  -是的
- With Liam? - Yeah.
我要去见我的律师
Well, I was gonna go meet with my lawyer,
打算带利亚姆一起去的
but I was gonna take Liam with me.
不了  谢谢  来吧
No, thanks. Come on.
-利普  -来吧
- Lip... - There you are.
那是个意外
It was an accident.
我们到楼下穿外衣
We're gonna put your coat on downstairs.
可以吗  好吗  好吗
Is that okay? Yeah? Yeah?
处理好自己的破事
Sort your shit out.
那个加拉格家的孩子的姐姐
That Gallagher kid's sister
给他弟弟吃可卡因
gave his baby brother cocaine.
我敢说  他之后就变智障了
Dude, I bet he's retarded now from it, huh?
绝对的
Totally.
可卡因小弟
Cocaine baby brother.
-可卡因小弟  -可卡因小弟
- C-c-c-cocaine baby brother. - Cocaine baby brother.
智障小加拉格  可卡因小弟
Retarded little Gallagher. Cocaine baby brother.
可卡因小弟
Cocaine baby brother.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
你开玩笑吧
Are you fucking kidding me?
什么时候能完事儿
When's this thing gonna be done?
是啊  你们安营扎寨的地方
Yeah, sure, it's not your business
又不是你们自家的门店
you're camped out in front of.
我服了  有人花钱雇你们
Unbelievable, someone pays you
站在洞旁边干瞪眼
for hole standing.
这么好的工作我上哪找  说真的
How do I get a job like that? Seriously?
这就是你们的工作
This is what you're doing?
你们就看着他一个人干活
You're just staring at that one guy working?
伙计
Hey, buddy.
你干完活之后
When you're done with work,
进来喝瓶啤酒
come on in for a beer.
但是就你一个  他们不行
But just you, not them!
好好品尝咖啡吧
Enjoy your coffee.
洞边儿站着的衰人
Fucking hole standers.
酒桶呢
Where's the keg?
现在喝酒早了点吧
A little early to be drinking, isn't it?
妈的
Shit.
酒桶呢
Where's the keg?
你找哪种酒桶
What kind of keg you looking for?
我们有老式的  舒立兹啤酒  米克劳啤酒
We got old style, Schlitz, Michelob--
不是一桶酒  混蛋  装钱的酒桶
Not a keg of beer, asshole! The keg with the money in it!
不知道你在说什么
No idea what you're talking about.
狗娘养的的
Son of a fucking bitch!
是我的钱  狗逼
That's my money, bitches!
是我的钱
That's my money!
狗逼  是我的钱啊
Bitches, that's my fucking money!
都这会儿了你们还光站着
Even now you're just gonna stand there and do nothing?
那帮熊孩子把我抢了
Those fucking kids robbed me!
至少帮我把胶带撕下来吧
Could you at least help me get this duct tape off?
操  你妈逼  我操  操
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
寝室
Dorm.
是啊  寝室里有什么
Yeah, and what's in a dorm?
嬉皮士
Hipsters.
嬉皮士  很好
Hipsters. Very good.
很好  好了  好吧
Very good. All right, come on.
飞咯
Going up.
来吧
There we go.
-天呐  -妈的
- Jesus! - Oh, shit.
对不起  对不起
Sorry. Sorry.
又不是我的房间
You know, it's not like it's my room or anything.
好了  我穿好了
Okay. Fine. I'm dressed.
好了
All right.
-过来  伙计  -这是谁呀
- Come here, buddy. - Who's this?
利亚姆  他是我弟弟
Liam. He's my kid brother.
你好  利亚姆
Hi, liam.
我只是来拿本书
You know, I'm just grabbing a book.
马上就走
And we're gonna get out of here.
你肯定有姐妹会
I'm sure you have some kind of a sorority,
拉拉队  圆桌会议  女生会议什么的
cheerleader, mensa, vagina meeting or something.
利亚姆  你喜欢克莱门氏橘吗
Hey, Liam, do you like clementines?
不
No!
没事的  伙计  拿着
It's okay, buddy. Go ahead.
这不是球  是好吃的  给你
It's not a ball, it's food. Here.
很好
It's good.
-你要吗  -不用了
- You? - No.
那个巧克力你要打开吃吗
But if you're cracking open that Toblerone.
谢谢
Thanks.
我父母每周都给我送个爱心包裹
My parents send me this care package crap once a week.
是啊  我父母  也给我送爱心包裹
Yeah, my parents, they sent me a care package too.
说真的  随便拿
Seriously, take anything you want.
-想要什么就直说  -什么
- Or if you have a request. - What?
库兹勒后背长粉刺
Yeah, Kuzner was getting backne,
我就跟我爸说我需要祛痘膏
so I told my dad that I needed accutane.
他给我送了一个6个月的药量
Sent me a six-month 'script.
都不知道不是我用
Never knew it wasn't for me.
他是医生之类的吗
Wow. Is he a doctor or something?
不  只是人脉广而已
No. Just connected.
-在迈阿密  -你家在迈阿密吗
- Miami. - Is that where you're from?
一起住了这么久  你才知道
After all these months, huh?
抱歉
Sorry.
我可以帮你看利亚姆
Hey, um, I could watch Liam for you if you wanted.
-你上课的时候  -不  没关系
- Like, while you're in class. - Ah, no. That's okay.
我五点之前都没事
I don't have anything till 5:00.
不用了  我们家
Yeah, no, we just went through
最近出了点乱子
some pretty serious shit at home.
导致现在我保护意识特别强  是吧
So I'm being kind of protective of him right now. Right?
我半小时给你发一张照片
I'll send you a text picture every 30 minutes.
好吧  有事给我打电话
Yeah, well, call me, you know, if there's a problem.
好的  别担心  没事的
Yeah, don't worry. Everything will be fine.
阿曼达会照顾你几小时
Hey, Amanda's gonna watch you for a few hours.
-可以吗  伙计  -好的
- Is that okay, buddy? - Okay.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
嗨  老爹  老爸
Hi, pops. Poppy?
爸爸
Daddy?
还在想要叫你什么
Still trying to figure out what to call you.
又在写博客了吗
Working on your blog again, huh?
五章了
Five chapters.
老天  这是什么味儿
Oh, my god. What's that smell?
汉堡王  我给你买了个皇堡
Burger king. I got you a whopper.
拿出去  拿出去
Get it out! Get it out!
老天  对不起
Oh, oh, my goodness. I'm sorry.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
这味道恶心到你了吗
The smell did it, huh?
这不明摆着呢吗
You need more proof than this?
让我把这条臭烘烘的毯子换掉
Let's get you off these stinky sheets.
反正也该换了
Time to change them anyway.
小心点  我的纸
Be careful. My papers.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
我好冷  把烟管给我
I'm cold. Give me my pipe.
爸  黛比和利普跟我说
Oh, pops, Debbie and Lip asked me
不能再让你在家抽大麻了
not to let you light up in the house anymore.
今天早晨和他们小吵了一架
Had a little run-in with them this morning.
他们对我可不太感冒
Don't think they like me very much.
去他们的
Well, screw them.
我想什么时候抽就什么时候抽
I'll light up any time I want.
如果我愿意  我会把烟雾
I'll blow smoke in their eyes
吐到他们眼睛里  直到他们哭出来
until they cry if I feel like it.
利普说社工随时可能来访
Lip said the social worker's gonna show up unannounced.
让社工吃屎去吧
Yeah, the social worker can bite my ball bag.
又不是我把利亚姆扔在一堆可卡因里的
I'm not the one who let Liam get into a pile of coke.
你知道那是意外
You know that was an accident.
拜托  你在干吗
Oh, come on. What are you doing?
我们必须好好表现
We have to be on our best behavior.
我很疼
I'm in pain.
他们可能最终会被送进寄养家庭
They could end up in foster care.
你不想让大家都聚在一起吗
Don't you want to keep this family together?
他们在毒害你
They're poisoning you.
就是这样
That's what's going on.
总有一天你会背叛我的  记住我的话
You'll turn against me, you mark my words.
你怎么能这么说  收回去
How can you say that? Take it back!
操你妹
Fuck you.
我永远永远都不会背叛你
I would never, ever turn against you.
是吗  那来证明
Yeah? Well, then prove it.
把烟管给我
Give me my pipe.
要不我把下次的奥施康定给你怎么样
How about I give you your next oxy instead, huh?
这是个好主意
Oh, that's a good idea.
还算有点脑子
Now you're thinking.
你会没事的  走个形式罢了
You'll be fine. It's just a formality.
等厕所的队太长了
The bathroom line took forever.
外面有个人  来这儿的原因
There's a guy out there who's here
是他往孩子他妈身上撒漂白剂了
because he threw bleach on his baby's mama.
按法官既定日程
On your honor's preliminary hearing calendar,
开庭审理第S6974356号案件
calling case S6974356.
伊利诺斯州控告菲奥娜·加拉格
State of Illinois versus Fiona Gallagher.
格雷格·杰夫瑞斯代表伊利诺斯州
Greg Jeffreys on behalf of the state of Illinois.
玛丽亚·薇达尔代表菲奥娜·加拉格
Maria Vidal on behalf of Fiona Gallagher,
-谁在我左边  -早上好
- Who's on my left. - Good morning.
加拉格小姐  在传讯中
Ms. Gallagher, at your arraignment,
你为自己提出无罪辩护
you entered a plea of not guilty.
-是否仍旧有效  -是的  法官
- Is that still your plea? - Absolutely, your honor.
杰夫瑞斯先生  公诉方在此案件上
And Mr. Jeffreys, where does the government
-看法为何  -法官大人
- stand on this case? - Your honor,
我们有足够的证据证明
we have enough evidence to proceed with possession
其犯有危害儿童安全罪
and child endangerment.
"危害儿童安全罪"
"Child endangerment"?
那是个意外
It was an accident.
杰夫瑞斯先生  你就此
Mr. Jeffreys, what evidence
有什么证据需要提交
have you submitted at this point?
这是负责逮捕的警官给出的报告
The police report from the arresting officer,
其中包括被告承认有罪
which includes an admission of guilt from the defendant,
从受害人脸上和手上
the cocaine removed from the face
收集到的可卡因
and the hands of the victim,
以及一份毒理学报告
and a toxicology report
指出在儿童被送进急诊室时
indicating the levels of the drug
毒品在其体内的含量
in the child's system when he was admitted to the E.R.
我方要求被告至少
We'll be asking for a minimum
在州监狱服刑五年
of five years in state prison.
什么
What?
这是我方诉求  法官大人
It is our hope, your honor,
希望法庭能考虑到
that the court will take into consideration
这是我委托人的初犯
that this is my client's first offense,
并考虑到政府在去年赋予了她
and that the state granted her guardianship
对于五个兄弟姐妹的监护权
of her five siblings last year.
薇达尔小姐  我强烈建议你与检察官
Miss Vidal, I urge you and the A.D.A.
在法庭外商讨这些细节
to discuss this matter outside of my courtroom.
达成个协议  待会儿呈上辩诉协议
Work something out. Come back with a plea bargain.
-是的  法官大人  -是的  法官大人
- Yes, your honor. - Yes, your honor.
-休庭  -怎么回事
- You're dismissed. - What's going on?
好事  走吧
Good news. Come on.
米奇在哪儿
Where's Mickey?
求你们别理我
No, please don't answer.
该死的  你们这辈子就不能做点有意义的事
God forbid, you do something meaningful with your lives.
你应该去为政府工作
You should work for the city.
社会需要你们
You have qualities they're looking for.
你他妈在这儿干嘛
Hey, what the hell are you doing here?
我需要把枪
I need a gun.
你想毙了谁
Who you gonna kill?
-你喷古龙水了吗  -没有
- You wearing cologne? - No.
是肯亚塔的香水皂什么的
It's Kenyatta's perfume soap shit.
你用了别人的肥皂
You use another dude's soap?
所以呢
So what?
上面会有阴毛的
It's got pubes on it.
-没有  -当然有
- No, it doesn't. - Yes, it does.
谁的香皂上没有阴毛
What guy doesn't have pubes on his soap?
我的香皂上就没有
My soap doesn't have pubes on it.
那是因为你从来不洗阴毛
Well, obviously, you're not washing your pubes.
你来就是为了跟我讨论阴毛的事吗
You came all the way down here to talk about my pubes?
给我把枪
Just give me a gun.
你在城南开酒吧
You run a bar on the south side.
你他妈居然没有枪
How the fuck do you not have a gun?
并非人人都是恶棍
Not everyone's a thug.
不过你到底要干嘛
What you need it for, anyway?
艾莱柏被劫了
Alibi got robbed.
他们偷了我放钱的酒桶
They stole the keg that I keep the money in.
等等  卖淫的钱吗
Wait, wait. The rub and tug money?
鉴于那是我最近
Considering it's the only money
唯一的进账项目  没错
that I'm pulling in these days, yeah.
你就放个小桶里吗
You keep that in a fucking keg?
-我不相信银行  -小凯  那是我的钱
- I don't trust the banks. - Kev, that's my money.
不  那是我的钱  30%给你
No, it's my money with 30% going to you.
30%  谁想到这个的
30 per-- who came up with that?
-我们应该对半分  -扯淡
- We're 50/50. - Bullshit.
-对半分  酒吧是我的  -妓女是我的
- 50/50? It's my bar. - My whores.
是吗  那你自己去保护你的妓女们
Yeah? Well, get your ass down there and protect your whores.
本该由你提供安保措施的
You're supposed to be providing security.
-只分我30%  我才不干  -怎么了
- Not for 30% I'm not. - What's going on?
这位动作巨星让别人偷了我们的钱
Steven Seagal here let somebody steal our cash.
因为你阴毛控的丈夫不司其职
Because your pube-loving husband wasn't doing his job.
你要去哪儿
Hey, where you going?
我要去处理一些重要的事
I gotta take care of something important.
我会尽快回去酒吧
I'll be down to the bar to protect your 7-foot ass
保护你这七尺大汉的
as soon as I can.
不行  如果有危险  我们不能工作
No, we cannot work if it's dangerous.
一点都不危险
It's not dangerous.
一天之内不会被抢劫两次
It's not gonna get robbed twice in a day.
万一那样的话  拜托你这次能不能
If it does, can you please shoot them
直接爆了他们的头
in the fucking face this time?
你知道怎么用这玩意吗
You know how to use this thing?
我当然知道怎么用
Of course I know how to use it.
老天
Oh, my god.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thanks. Appreciate it.
他怎么说
What did he say?
现在  我们所有的对话都享有免责权
At this point, all our conversations need to be privileged.
什么
What?
我得跟菲奥娜单独谈谈
I need to talk to Fiona alone.
我刚好约了医生
I have a doctor's appointment anyway.
你一个人没问题吧
You gonna be okay?
-我回头再找你  -好的
- I'll talk to you later. - Okay.
我们边走边说  我20分钟后得赶去库克县
Walk with me. I gotta be at Cook county in 20 minutes.
我问杰夫瑞斯先生
I asked mr. Jeffreys
是否同意改为3年的缓刑监护期
If he'd agree to three years probation.
那真是太好了啊
That'd be great.
不敢保证可行  但有那个可能
No promises. But it is possible.
但你必须认罪
You'd have to plead guilty.
也就是说你会留下犯罪记录
That means you'll have a criminal record.
但不用去坐牢
But no jail time?
就算坐牢也会很短的
Very little if any.
多短
How very little?
60天吧  最多90天
60 days? 90 tops?
等等  我可以获得缓刑
Wait, so I get probation,
但我还得去蹲三个月的大牢吗
But I still have to go to jail for three months?
跟他们提出的刑期相比已经很短了
It's only for a fraction of the time they're asking for.
我不能再回监狱
I can't go back to jail.
我们不如等着看看他提出什么量刑主张吧
Why don't we just wait and see what he proposes?
我们能申请庭审吗
Can we go to trial?
菲奥娜  我每天都做这种事  我告诉你
Fiona, I do this every day. I'm telling you.
我们申请缓刑成功的机会很大
We have a great argument for probation.
你这是初犯
You're a first time offender,
而且你打电话叫了急救人员
And you called the paramedics.
地方检察官并不希望你因为这种案子
D.A. Doesn't want you clogging up the jail
就进监狱  占用了刑罚资源
or this case gumming up the system,
让他们无暇处理真正的刑事案件
Taking them away from real criminal cases.
但利亚姆的遭遇实在太吓人了
But what happened with Liam was horrific.
陪审团肯定会讨厌你的
A jury is gonna hate you.
我可以协商出一个好结果的
I can negotiate the hell out of this.
我非常不想再进监狱
I don't want to go to jail at all.
我们并非事事都能如愿
Well, we don't get everything we want.
成功的商谈就是双方都觉得
And a good negotiation is when both sides
自己吃大亏了
Feel like they got screwed.
热力学第三定律简单来说就是
The third law of thermodynamics simply stated is
在绝对零度  任何完美晶体的熵
The entropy of a perfect crystal at absolute zero...
其实就是零
is exactly equal to zero.
我们之前讨论过了
Now, from our earlier discussions,
熵是对什么的衡量
We know that entropy is a measure of what?
混乱程度
Disorder.
而晶体是固态的
And a crystal is a solid
其原子  分子和离子的
Whose atoms or molecules or ions
排列方式是怎样的
Are arranged in what kind of pattern?
-有序排列  -很好
- Ordered. - Very good.
我们明天再继续说  别忘了
We'll pick this up tomorrow. Don't forget.
今晚5点前把作业发到我的邮箱
Assignments emailed to me by 5:00 p.M. this evening.
萨科教授  我很抱歉
Hey, professor Sacco. I'm sorry.
我觉得我今晚可能交不了作业
I don't think I'm gonna be able to get my assignment in tonight.
我家里出了点事
I had a bit of a family crisis.
那你大概什么时候能交
When do you think you'll have it?
明天吧
Tomorrow.
每迟交一天  我就把你的分数降半级
Every day it's late, I'm docking you a half a grade.
明白吗
Comprende?
好的  明白了  谢谢您
Yes. Comprende. Thank you.
奶酪火腿鸡排是什么
What's chicken cordon bleu?
反正你在马蒂加厨房是做不出这道菜的
Nothing you can make with what's in Matty's kitchen.
那我该给他做什么当晚餐啊
Well, what should I make him for dinner then?
你们什么时候又复合了
Since when did you guys get back together?
菲奥娜被捕时  他帮了我
He helped when Fiona got arrested.
幸亏我没去勾搭他
Good thing I didn't hit on him.
我本来真打算去的
I was totally gonna.
代数真是太他妈荒谬了
This algebra crap is redic.
谁他妈会在乎数学啊
Who gives a shit about math?
-我怎么会需要用到数学啊  -大概一直要用吧
- When am I ever gonna use it? - Probably all the time.
我直接抄你的算了
Let me just copy yours.
意大利面和肉丸怎么样
How about spaghetti and meatballs?
任何有"丸"的都很好
Anything with balls in it is good.
好吧
Okay.
你他妈最近是去哪儿了啊
Where the hell have you been?
加里和我分手了
Gary broke up with me
因为他父母不希望他多养个孩子
'cause his parents don't want him to have a baby.
所以我自残了
So I cut myself.
-什么  -然后被我妈发现了
- What? - Then my mother found out.
发现你自残吗
That you cut yourself?
不  是发现加里和我分手了
No, that Gary broke up with me.
所以她今早把我拖去了他家
So she dragged me to his house this morning.
但他还在睡觉
But he was still asleep.
然后我妈和他妈大打了一架
So my mom and his mom got into this huge fight.
然后警察都来了
Then the cops came.
所以我才上学迟到了
And that's how come I'm late for school.
但你为什么要自残呢
But why'd you cut yourself?
是啊  那好傻
Yeah. That was stupid.
我唯一被男人甩的那次
The one time a guy dumped me,
就狂吐了一番而已
I just made myself puke.
你觉得加里还会跟你复合吗
Think Gary will get back together with you?
他说他会考虑的
He said he'd think about it.
你家里也该发生一次紧急事件
You should totally have a family emergency.
那样他就会回心转意的
That'll make him come back.
-马蒂就是这样的  -好吧  什么紧急事件呢
- Worked with matty. - Okay, like what?
你可以跟他说你家狗生病了
Mm, you could tell him your dog got sick.
或者说你被人侵犯了
Or that you got molested.
那真是个好理由
That's a good one.
下午好  抱歉让你久等了
Good afternoon. Sorry about the wait.
刚刚不得不为一个病人的子宫颈缝了几针
Had to throw a stitch into a patient's cervix
以防她的孩子早产
Before her little critter slipped out too early.
不过幸好母子平安
But we're all good.
现在是时候看看你肚子里的宝宝们了
And it's time to look at your little critters.
-怎么  小凯没来吗  -在工作
- What, no Kev? - Work.
你最近感觉怎么样
And how have you been feeling lately?
肥得跟猪一样
Bloated and fat.
有什么问题吗
Something wrong?
我能看到两个胎儿
Well, I have the two.
但看不到第三个
But I can't seem to find the other.
再找一下
Let's see.
有时候胎儿会躲起来
Sometimes they hide.
好吧  检查一下我膀胱后面
Yeah, well, check behind my bladder
我一天大概要尿50次呢
'cause I've been peeing, like, 50 times a day.
你到底在哪儿呢
Now where are you?
好像出现胚儿被吸收的情况了
Well, I think we might have a fetal resorption.
那他妈是什么玩意儿
What the hell is that?
怀上多胞胎就容易出现这种情况
It happens with multiples.
当一个胚胎不够强壮生存下去时
When the fetus isn't strong enough to survive,
其他胚胎就会将其吸收
The others sometimes absorb it.
吸收
"Absorb it"?
你是说吃掉吗
As in eat it?
倒也不能那么说  但差不多吧
Mm, not exactly. But yes.
我的其中一个孩子已经死了吗
One of my babies is gone?
但另外两个看上去很健康
But the other two look very healthy.
是因为我养胎不当吗
Is it something that I did?
不是  只是大自然以它自己的方式
Nope, just mother nature's way
淘汰掉孱弱的后代而已
Of selecting out the weaker baby.
看着挺帅嘛
Looking fine.
-滚蛋  -我就喜欢强硬的小伙子
- Fuck off. - I like 'em rough.
我叫斯科特  你想出去一起玩玩吗
I'm Scott. You want to get out of here?
不  我不想...
No, I don't want to--
你见过这个孩子吗
You seen this kid?
哎呀  你喜欢瘦猴型的呀
Oh. You like 'em skinny.
如果你喜欢  我也可以减肥30磅的
I could lose 30 pounds if you wanted.
30磅  去你妈逼的  老兄
30 poun-maybe in your ass, man.
经理在哪儿
Where's the manager?
喂  你是经理吗
Yo. You the manager?
当然是大爷我在问你啊
I'm gonna take a wild stab it was me.
见过这人吗
You seen this kid?
他叫伊恩
His name is Ian.
从来没见过
Never saw him before.
你再看一眼怎么样
Why don't you take a look again?
他以前在这里工作  所以你肯定见过
He used to work here so I'm pretty sure you have.
这里每天人来人往
I can't keep track of every twink
我又不能盯着每个人看  好吗
who comes and goes in this place, all right?
好吧
Okay.
这人自从几天前
This twink went awol a couple days ago
你的保镖把他哥和他妹赶了出去之后
after your bouncer kicked
就不见了
his brother and kid sister out into the street.
-这事你记得吗  -听着  小崽子
- You remember that? - Look, you little tweaker.
你不是第一个了
You think you're the first one to come in here
经常有人来这叫唤  说有个美男
boo-hooing about some cocktail slut
在厕所给他撸了一管
who jacked you off in the bathroom,
说是此生真爱  然后就消失了
told you it was true love, and then disappeared?
有点新意好吗
Trust me. You're not.
所以你不如点杯酒
So why don't you buy yourself a drink
然后爱上其他人吧  好吗
and fall in love with somebody else?
你说我是同性恋吗
You calling me gay?
拜托  亲爱的
Oh. Please, honey.
贾斯汀·比伯都没你娘
You make Justin Bieber look straight.
听着  我知道你知道他在哪
Now, I know you know where he is, dick breath.
要么告诉我他在哪  不然我就以
So you're gonna tell me, or I'm gonna shut this
违禁物品持有罪
come-hole down over possession,
还有卖淫罪把这里关了
intent to sell, and prostitution.
-懂了吗  -他在另一家分店里
- Okay? - He's at our other location.
在男孩城的妖精尾巴俱乐部
Fairy Tail in Boystown.
谢了
Thank you.
也不难嘛
That so difficult?
有人来了吗
Yo, anybody coming?
还没  动作快点  麻利点  快
No, but hurry up, man. Apurate. Come on.
好吧
Alright.
冷冻汉堡肉饼不错
Frozen burger patties look good.
兄弟  这么多东西
Gringo, how you gonna get out with all that stuff
你怎么偷拿出去
and not get caught?
我不从正门走
I'm not going out the front.
你去扔垃圾的时候
Okay, take the trash out,
把这个放在垃圾桶最上面
put this on top of the dumpster.
我回家的时候去拿
I'll grab it on my way home.
你比看起来聪明很多嘛
You're not as dumb as you look.
你知道的吧
You know that, right?
应该可以了
That should do it.
-没问题吧  -放心吧  好
- Got that? - Got it, got it. All right.
回头见  兄弟
See you later, gringo.
你好啊  怎么样
Hey. How you doing?
汤博乐上居然有饮酒博客
Tumblr drinking blogs there are out there?
我写得肯定比这群蠢货要好
I could write a better one than these douche bags.
等等  你父亲在监狱的时候
Wait, so your mother was dating two different guys
你母亲同时有两个男友
while your father was in prison.
至少两个
That we knew of.
"抽了一碗掺了可卡因的大麻
"Smoking a coke-laced bowl of weed
史上最嗨的一次"
is the best high ever"?
太业余了
Amateurs.
她难道不怕他发现吗
Wasn't she afraid he'd find out?
发现了  提前释放
He did. Got an early release.
回家就看到
Walked in on her screwing Vavoo...
她和哪个从饭店带回来的服务员在床上
some busboy she brought home from the restaurant.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
他什么反应
What did he do?
那个服务员吗  吓尿了
Vavoo? He crapped himself.
我爸的反应一如既往
My father did what he always did.
-揍了我一顿  -为什么打你
- Beat on me. - Why you?
因为是我的错啊  什么都是我的错
It was my fault. It was always my fault.
我妈完全没事  我被狠揍了一顿
My mom got away scot-free. I got a whupping.
说我应该看着点她
Said I should've been keeping her in line.
那克莱顿叔叔  瓦提叔叔和杰瑞叔叔呢
What about uncle Clayton and Wyatt and Jerry?
那是他最喜欢的人  你问这些干什么
There were his favorites. Why do you care so much?
希望跟你亲近点嘛
Just want us to get closer
毕竟时间有限
since we have limited time.
时间有限  时间很无限好吗
Limited ti-- we do not have limited time.
该死的
Jesus!
你到底什么毛病
What's the matter with you?
-我...  -我操
- I-- - Jesus!
你写回忆录不就是因为这个吗
Isn't this why you're writing your memoirs?
我才不是在写回忆录
I am not writing my memoirs.
这是我送给人类的礼物
This is my gift to humankind.
这是我要出版的科普书籍
This is my trade book.
人们一定会花巨资买我的知识
People will pay go money for my knowledge.
你说得对  你说得对
You're right, you're right.
你信那些医生的话干什么
Why are you listening to the doctors?
他们说的话根本屁都不算
They don't know what the fuck they're talking about.
我们  我们有的是...
We have-- we have all--
我操  操他妈的
Fuck. Oh, fuck!
-呼吸  -我的天哪
- Oh, hey, breathe. - Dear god.
-深呼吸  -我操
- Breathe, okay? - Shit.
深呼吸
Breathe.
-继续呼吸  -真操蛋
- Breathe. - Oh, god.
我不是故意惹你生气的
I didn't mean to upset you.
我们有的是时间  好不好
We have all the time in the world, okay?
我早就说过  你跟其他孩子一样
I told you, you're just like the rest of my kids.
不  我不一样
No, I'm not.
对不起  我收回那些话
Please, I-I-I take it back.
好吗  我收回
Okay? I take it back.
我们的时间多得是
We don't have limited time.
废话  当然了
You're goddamn right we don't.
好的  好  来吧  来
Okay, okay. Come on, come on.
我帮你揉揉
Come here. Here.
不要  我要睡觉
No! I need a nap.
怎么  你这是生我气了吗
Oh. What, are you mad at me now?
我保证  我再也不会那样说了
Look, I promise, I'll never say it again.
我给你准备了礼物
I have a present for you.
本来打算等你病重时再送
I was saving it until you got really sick.
现在就给你吧
I could give it to you now.
是我想的那东西吗
Is that what I think it is?
我是不是好样的
Did I do good?
扶...  扶我起来
Help--help me. Help me sit up.
我操
Oh, fuck.
-疼死爹了  -好了
- Oh, god! - Okay.
我去接恰奇
I need to go get Chuckie.
很快就回来
Be back lickety-split.
你慢慢去吧
Take your time.
都听我说
All right, listen up.
今天早上酒吧被抢了
Bar got robbed this morning.
是吗  他们抢了什么
Yeah? What'd they take?
鸡尾酒餐巾吗
The cocktail napkins?
整整六百块
$600, for your information.
是谁偷的
So who stole it?
猜不到  谁偷的
I give up. Who?
不  我不是让你们猜是谁偷的
No, not who stole it, like, guess who stole it.
我是问你们这群混蛋里谁偷了老子的钱
Who stole it like which one of you fuckers stole my money?
你为什么觉得是我们偷的
Why do you think we stole your money?
因为你们知道我把钱藏在哪里
Because you knew where I hid it.
-哪里  -在酒桶里啊
- Where? - In the damn keg!
是吗  现在知道了
Ooh. We do now.
再问一次  谁偷了我的钱
I said who stole my money.
怎么  现在谁都有枪了吗
What, everyone has a gun?
《圣经》说我们有权持有武器
Bible says we have the right to bear arms.
-所以我就带了  -是《宪法》规定的
- So I bear arms. - It's the constitution.
真的吗
No shit?
反正我会盯着你们的
Well, I'm keeping my eye on all of you.
凯文先生  现在没了桶
Where should I put the money now, Mr. Kevin,
钱要放哪里
if there's no keg?
给我吧
Give it to me.
我要放在没有人敢碰的地方
I'm gonna put it where no one dares to touch.
从现在起  谁都不能信任  帕科  知道吗
From now on, we trust no one, Paco. No one.
-宝贝  -宝贝  孕检怎么样
- Hey babe. - Hey, baby. How was the appointment?
我们只剩下两个孩子了
Oh, well, we're down to two babies.
不会吧
No.
怎么回事
What happened?
休伊吃了杜威
Huey ate Dewey.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
不  医生说多胞胎经常会发生这种事
No, Doc says it happens all the time with multiples.
不够强壮的胎儿
If one's not strong enough,
就会消失
they just go away, poof.
那另外两个没事吧
Are the other two okay?
我都不知道该怎么说了
I don't know how to feel about this.
是啊  我也是
No, me either.
有点如释重负  是吧
It's bit of a relief, right?
算是吧
Sort of.
我已经做好养四个孩子的打算了
I was getting used to the idea of having four babies.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
现在可不是个好时候告诉她酒吧被打劫了吧
Probably a bad time to tell her the place got robbed, huh?
-什么  -汤米  闭嘴
- What? - Tommy, shut up!
小维  别担心
V, don't worry.
以后再也没人敢抢我的东西了
No one's taking any more shit from me.
我的孩子  我的钱
My babies, my money--
我已经做好准备了
I'm battening down the hatches.
我要好好保护这里
I'm putting a force field around us now.
-宝贝  -照看好属于我的东西
- Babe. - Taking care of what's mine.
过来  让我保护你
Come here. Get in my force field.
老兄
Hey, man. What's up?
你他妈想怎么样
What the hell do you want?
今早在校车上听到你们
Heard you talk about my little brother, Liam,
谈论我弟利亚姆了
on the bus this morning.
你说你那个智障弟弟吗
You mean your retarded brother?
是的  他想让你俩见见他两个朋友
Yeah. He wants you to meet two of his friends.
你那智障弟弟还有朋友
Your retarded brother has friends?
是啊  见过小智和小障
Yeah. Meet Mongo and Loid.
我操  他好像撞断了我的鼻梁
Fuck. I think he broke my nose.
活该
Sucks for you.
你弟还是个智障
Brother's still gonna be retarded.
脑损伤谁也没法子  加拉格
Can't ice a damaged brain, Gallagher.
蠢货
Schmuck.
有人吗
Hello?
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?
做肉丸意面
Making spaghetti and meatballs.
在网上查的食谱
Looked it up online.
真心不难
It's really not that hard.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in?
管理员
The super.
她帮你开的门
She unlocked my apartment for you?
不  她告诉我你把备用钥匙藏在哪
Nope. Told me where you kept the spare key.
好吧  她为什么要告诉你
Okay, why would she do that?
因为我跟她说今天是我们的纪念日
Because I told her it was our anniversary
我想给你个惊喜
and I wanted to surprise you.
今天是我们约会一个月纪念日
We've been dating a month today.
你不记得也没关系
Um, it's okay if you don't remember.
两个月纪念日再补偿我好了
You can just make it up to me on our two-month anniversary.
黛比  我们得谈谈
Okay, Debbie. We need to talk.
你能给艾丽牵牵线吗
Hey, can you fix Ellie up with someone?
她对象甩了她
Her boyfriend dumped her.
那个怀孕的姑娘吗
She the pregnant one?
我们不是已经分手了吗
I'm--I thought we said we weren't gonna date anymore.
有吗
We did?
就你那次过来我家
Yeah, that time you came over?
想做爱那次
You wanted to have sex?
我不太清楚到底什么情况
I wasn't clear about what happened.
好吧
Okay.
我们不能做男女朋友
We can't be boyfriend and girlfriend.
但利亚姆和菲奥娜出事时你都陪着我
But you were there for me with Liam and Fiona.
这是朋友都会做的事
Yeah, that's what friends do.
朋友
"Friends"?
小黛  我真的很喜欢你
Look, Deb. I really like you.
那为什么要跟我分手
But then why are you breaking up with me?
因为你太小了
Because you're too young.
我真该谎报年龄的
I should've lied about my age.
等你年长一些也许我们还能试试...
I mean, we can try again when you're older, but--
等到几岁
How much older?
16岁吧  我不知道
16? I don't know.
我哪里不好
What's wrong with me?
你没有不好  小黛  你很完美
Nothing, Deb. You're perfect.
你得跟你那个年纪的男生约会
You just--you gotta date guys your own age.
我也该跟我这个年纪的姑娘约会
I should probably date girls my own age.
晚餐很香
Dinner smells good.
我想回家了
I want to go home.
女人
Women...
我喜欢臃肿恶毒  不太聪明的
I like 'em fat, vicious, and not too smart.
也别搞心灵那套
Nothing spiritual either.
晚餐吃什么
Hey, what's for dinner?
带利亚姆上楼
Take Liam upstairs.
我来准备晚餐  好吗
I'll get it ready, okay?
学校同学说他是智障
Kids at school said he's retarded.
去他们的  他不是
Oh, fuck them. He's not retarded.
去清理一下  快点
Go clean up. Clean up.
时间到了  鸳鸯
Time's up, lovebirds.
起来
Get up.
他妈的给我起来  到我了
That means get the fuck up. It's my turn.
我回头再找你  柯蒂斯
I'll look for you later, Curtis.
柯蒂斯
"Curtis"?
-是你的艺名吗  -跳一支大腿舞25块
- Fucking stage name? - 25 bucks gets you a dance.
你说什么
Excuse me?
不想要就走开
Don't want to dance, you gotta move on.
好  行吧
Okay, all right.
25块买你的屁股是吧
25 bucks for your ass, huh?
以前你可从不向我收钱
Never had to pay for that shit before.
你过得好吗
So how's your day going so far?
我他妈过得好吗
How's my fucking day going?
开心吗
Having fun?
不  我不开心
No, I'm not having fun.
我他妈一整天都在找你这个毒鬼
I spent the whole day looking for your coked-out ass.
你家人很担心你
Your family's worried about you.
喂  搞毛啊
Hello? The fuck?
这样我没法说话  我们能出去说吗
I can't talk to you like this. Can we go outside?
这些基佬给你嗑了多少药
These fudge packers got so much snow up your beak,
你都扭得跟娘们一样了
you're tweaking like a little bitch.
25块只能跳一支舞
25 bucks only buys you one dance.
好吧  那去我家
Okay. Then let's go back to my place.
你可以清醒清醒
You can sober up a little bit.
咱们叙叙旧什么的
Catch up or some shit.
你告诉我这段日子都上哪去了
Tell me where you've been all this time.
很有意思
That was fun.
还想要的话再来找我
Find me if you want another one.
你他妈在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
你不想跟我走  无所谓
Look, you don't want to hang out with me, that's fine.
但你得给家里打个电话
You need to call your family.
你爸快死了  伊恩
Your dad's dying, Ian.
菲奥娜差点害死利亚姆
Fiona almost killed Liam.
给她打电话
Call her.
没事吧  柯蒂斯
Is everything okay here, Curtis?
-没事  罗杰  -那就好
- Everything's great, Roger. - Good.
那边那家伙看起来像是想要一段大腿舞
'Cause that guy over there looks like he may want a dance.
我这就去  谢了
I'm on it. Thank you.
好吧  别被泛白的阴毛呛到了
Okay. Don't choke on any gray pubes.
淡定  哥们  我这就走
Relax, shaft. I'm leaving.
你是智障了吗
Are you retarded now?
但愿你是在睡觉而不是智障迷糊
I hope you're sleeping and not in a retarded haze.
监狱什么样
What was jail like?
你弄纹身了吗
You get any tattoos?
幽闭恐怖
It was claustrophobic.
孤独悲伤
It's lonely, sad.
他们没把你头发剃了
They try to shave your head?
你看不出来这是假发吗
You can't tell this is a wig?
他们像畜生一样对待你
They treat you like cattle.
没人关心你
No one cares about you.
有没有人被砍哭
Anyone get stabbed?
再待久点的话可能会有
Probably if I was there longer.
连撒尿拉屎都没有隐私
You can't piss or shit in private.
最难过的是我不知道自己还能不能再见到你们
The worst part was not knowing if I'd see you guys again.
别把自己折腾进监狱
Don't end up there.
闻起来不错
Smells good.
是啊
Yeah.
这些东西哪儿弄来的
Where'd you get all this stuff?
学校
School.
谢谢
Thanks.
我参加了预审
So, I had my prelim hearing.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
如果我认罪  我的律师会帮我争取缓刑
My lawyer's gonna try to get me probation if I plead guilty.
好的
Okay.
不过可能还要进去一段时间
Might have to serve a little time though.
是吗  多久
Yeah? How long?
最多三个月
90 days or less.
好的
All right.
应该能应付得来
I suppose we'll manage.
或者我去受审
Or I could go to trial.
为什么要这么做
Why would you want to do that?
为什么不能呢
Why wouldn't I do that?
因为你会被判刑
Because you'll get convicted.
-这可说不定  -当然一定
- You dot know that. - Yes, I do.
-我犯了个错  -你有罪
- I made a mistake. - You're guilty.
-那是意外  -你差点害死利亚姆
- It was an accident. - You almost killed Liam!
你以为我不知道
You don't think I know that?
你以为我不够自责
You don't think I'm blaming myself enough already
还需要你来说我
so I need you to do it too?
败诉的话  要判多久
So how long are you in prison if, ah, if you lose?
五年
Five years.
到时我就快25岁了
So that makes me almost 25.
还在家里  看孩子
Still at home, taking care of the kids.
我能胜诉
I know I can win.
贫民窟一女孩把他瘾君子男友的毒品
Ghetto chick leaves her drug addict boyfriend's
给他三岁弟弟吃
coke out for her three-year-old brother to eat.
吃了有半克
Half a gram in the system.
没错  你肯定能胜诉
Yeah, you're right. You can totally win.
-我不是故意的  -但你还是做了
- I didn't do it on purpose. - Yeah, but you did it!
我只不过离开了两秒而已
I turned my back, for, like, two seconds,
然后我这辈子就完了  这公平吗
and now my life is ruined? How is that fair?
你是他的监护人
You're his guardian.
这是你的职责所在
You signed up for this.
我不能进监狱
I can't go back to jail.
当然  考虑的全是你
Of course, this is all about you.
是 全都是我
Yes, it's about me!
从来都没有考虑过我
Okay, 'cause it's never about me
现在终于轮到我了
and I'm finally making it about me!
然后呢  你要蹲五年监狱
So what, I'm supposed to drop out of school
我就得辍学了吗
while you do five years?
-我没罪  -利亚姆差点死了
- I'm not guilty! - Liam almost died!
都是因为你  是他妈你
And that was you! All fucking you!
你的毒品  你的男友  你的破人生
Your coke, your boyfriend, your fucked up life!
不是我的  好吗
It's not mine! All right?
弗兰克在厕所昏过去了
Frank's passed out up in the bathroom.
操
Oh, fuck.
靠
Shit.
他现在注射海洛因了
He's shooting heroin now?
他死了没
Is he dead?
没死  真倒霉
No, unfortunately not.
天啊
Oh, my god.
卡尔  拉着他的腿
Carl, grab his legs.
他浑身是屎
He shit himself.
好吧  拿条毛巾
All right, use a fucking towel.
我抬起来了  你呢
I got him. You got him?
往哪放
Where we taking him?
以前放哪儿就放哪儿  路边
Where we always do-- street.
怎么回事
What's going on?
臭死了
It smells up here.
很好  你回来了  你来处理
Good. You're home. You deal with him.
爸爸  怎么了
Daddy? What happened?
他昏过去了
He's unconscious.
-肯定是奥施康定吃多了  -得了吧
- Must have had too many oxys. - Save it.
快他妈把他抬出去  好吗
All right? Just get him the fuck out of the house.
-什么  我警告过你  快滚
- What? - I warned you. Now go!
卡尔  过来  把弗兰克房间里的东西
Carl, come here. Get rid of any evidence
收拾干净  好吗
in Frank's room, all right?
他太虚弱了  不能出去
He is too sick to leave the house.
少废话
Yeah, no shit!
你他妈的让他注射了海洛因
You just let him shoot a bunch of fucking "H"!
他痛得要死
He was in pain!
要是社工突然来了怎么办
What if the social worker had showed up right now?
-她没来  -这些孩子都会被送走
- But she didn't. - These kids would've been taken away.
你在乎过吗
And what do you care, huh?
你只是想做个爸爸的乖女儿
You just want to make nicey-nicey with daddy.
你快点给我滚出去
You get the fuck out of my house!
菲奥娜
Fiona?
你们得离开  萨咪
You have to go, Sammi.
老爹
Pops?
天啊
Oh, god.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  很好
Yeah. Hmm. Fine.
我们还可以一起玩
You know, we can still do stuff together.
是的  很好
Yeah. Great. Cool.
-看个电影  -很好  不错
- You know, go to movies... - Perfect. Sounds fun.
就像朋友一样出去玩
Hang out, like friends do.
回头再说
Talk to you later.
好的  再说吧
Yeah. I'll talk to you later.
-拜拜  -拜
- Bye. - Bye--
不要摔了他的腿  恰奇  好的
Don't bang his leg, Chuckie. Okay
一  二  三
One, two, three!
好难闻
It smells.
让一下
Excuse me!
黛比  利普把我们赶出来了
Debbie, Lip kicked us out.
-对不起  -没关系  爸爸
- I'm sorry. - It's okay, dad.
-对不起  -我们加把劲  小恰
- I'm sorry. - Okay, let's power through, Chuckles.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
我操了个
Holy fuck!
好冷
It's so cold.
你不冷吗
Aren't you cold?
不冷
No.
你的车呢
Where's your car?
我打车来的
I took a cab.
我来给你暖暖
I've gotta keep you warm.
你家里有药丸子吗
Got any party favors at your place?
你要什么有什么
Anything you want.
不到三分钟车就来了
Car will be here in under three minutes.
来之前  咱们做点什么呢
What should we do till then?
你这个死基佬怎么不去勾引像你一样的老头呢
Why don't you molest someone your own age, you Geritol fuck?
我靠
Ow! Fuck!
你这个禽兽
You're an animal.
又不是我对一个未成年的男孩
I'm not the one groping and licking
摸摸舔舔  对吧
on underage boys, am I?
-我们只是玩玩  -闭上臭嘴
- We're just having fun. - Shut the fuck up.
在柯蒂斯叫警察抓你之前  给他点封口费
Give Curtis some money before he calls the cops on you.
好好  给你  拿着
Okay. Okay. Here, take, here.
很好  谢谢
Good, good. Thank you.
给老子滚走
Get the fuck out of here.
快滚
Get out of here!
学学怎么像个爷们儿一样跑步
And learn how to run like a dude!
老天  伊恩
Jesus Christ, Ian.
你叫的车吗
You called for an Uber?
没错  我叫的车
Yeah, I called for an Uber.
好了  干得漂亮  各位
Okay. Good job, fellas.
就快到了
Almost there.
轻点  恰奇
Easy does it, Chuckie.
把他放进椅子里
Let's get him in the chair.
好了
Okay.
大功告成
There we go.
家  温馨的家呀
Home sweet home.
等等
Okay--wait, wait!
老天
God.
我们得把你弄出去
We gotta get you out of here.
好样的  恰奇
Good boy, Chuckie.
没想到你有这一手  小子
I didn't know you had it in you, boy.
希拉会不会生我的气
Is Sheila gonna be mad at me?
她出城了
She's out of town.
现在让我给你洗个澡吧  老爸
Now, dad, let's get you washed up, huh?
操
Fuck it.
最后一个问题  利亚姆
All right, last question, Liam.
你是否曾与无生命的物体成为朋友
Have you made friends with an inanimate object?
比如一盏台灯或者一张椅子
Like a lamp or chair?
完成了
All right.
我在提交你的答案
I'm submitting your answers.
看看你得了多少分
Let's see what your score is.
好消息
Good news.
恭喜
你只有13%弱智
你不是弱智
You're not retarded.
轮到你了
Now you.
好  我也来测测
All right. Now let's see.
是  不是
Yes. No.
是  不是  不是  是
Yes. No. No. Yes.
不是  是
No. Yes.
做完了
All right.
抱歉
你有82%是弱智
你这弱智电脑
This stupid fucking computer.
我的小兄弟都比这枪大三倍
My dick is like three times bigger than this gun.
你把子弹取出来了对吧
You took the bullets out, right?
取了  亲爱的  最听你话了
Yes, honey. Heard you loud and clear.
我靠
Oh, shit.
你看这被吸收的胎儿
Look at this fetus being reabsorbed.
胚胎吸收
小维  别再看那些鬼东西了
V, would you stop looking at that shit?
你会把自己吓出病来的
You're gonna freak yourself out.
忍不住
Oh. I can't help it.
子宫里的三胞胎没能保住
I couldn't protect my triplet in utero.
你最好确保
You better be damn well sure
我能在现实生活中保护好的的双胞胎
I'm gonna protect my twins in the real world.
我靠  宝贝  你点燃了我的欲火呢
Damn, baby. You're starting to turn me on.
什么
What?
通便了吗
No constipation?
腹胀口腔溃疡都没了吗
Or bloating or mucous?
它们哪里都没去
Oh, no, I still got them.
但我开始了解那些欲求不满的
But I'm starting to see what all those horny,
怀孕女性是什么感觉了
pregnant women were talking about.
过来
Come here.
终于
Oh. Yes, finally.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
跨进去
There we go.
好了
Okay.
真舒服
Feels good.
-很温暖  -认真洗洗
- Warm. - Scrub up.
没关系  有我呢  有我呢
It's okay. I got you, I got you.
有我呢  有我呢
I got you. I got you.
-差点跌倒了  -没关系
- Almost fell. - It's okay.
扶着浴缸边上
Hold on to the side there, okay?
撑着点
Okay? Just hang on.
等一会儿
Hang on a second.
我马上来
I'll be right there.
现在
Now...
让点地方给萨咪
Make room for Sammi.
抓着我  我扶着你
Grab on. I got you.
不不不  不要
No, no. No, no, no.
我不会咬你  好吗
I'm not gonna bite. Okay?
来吧
Come on.
转过来  扶着我
Here. Come to me.
来  爸爸  过来
Come on, dad. Come over here.
这就对了  这就对了
There you go. There you go.
这就对了
There you go.
没那么糟  不是吗
That's not so bad, is it?
把你洗得干干净净
Get you all cleaned up. Okay.
维达尔女士  杰夫瑞斯先生
Ms. Vidal, Mr. Jeffreys,
据我了解  你们已经达成协议
I understand you've come up with a deal.
-是的  法官大人  我们已经...  -除了一点
- Yes, your honor, we ha... - Except for one point.
我们愿意遵从您的裁决
We'd like to defer to you on this count.
你们商量的结果是什么
What have you worked out so far?
法官大人  如果加拉格女士愿意
Your honor, in exchange for a guilty plea
承认犯下危害儿童罪以及藏毒罪
of child endangerment and possession,
检察院愿意让加拉格女士
the state is willing to offer Ms. Gallagher
缓刑三年  三年中
a three-year probation
随时可能进行强制性的药物检查
with mandatory random drug testing
还要参加200小时的养育儿童课程
as well as 200 hours of both parenting classes
以及匿名解毒协会
and narcotics anonymous meetings.
我们建议将加拉格女士送进教养所
The state would also recommend that Ms. Gallagher
进行为期90天的改造
serve 90 days in the state penitentiary.
鉴于这是我客户第一次触犯法律
And I'm suggesting that since this is my client's
而且她已经服过刑  我建议
first offense, and she already has time served,
将改造时间降为30天
that she only do 30 days.
-说完了吗  -是的  法官大人  说完了
- Is that everything? - Yes, your honor, it is.
说完了  法官大人
Yes, your honor.
杰夫瑞斯先生  我将把你提出的
Mr. Jeffreys, I will be reducing
200小时养育儿童课程与匿名戒毒会
your request from 200 hours of parenting
时间缩短为100小时
and NA meetings to 100 hours.
同时  我也不认为把加拉格女士
And since I do not believe justice will be served
送进监狱正义就能够得到伸张
by additional jail time for Ms. Gallagher,
我将把送进教养所的部分
I'll sign off on her completion
从协议中划掉
of that part of the plea bargain.
是的  法官大人
Yes, your honor.
不用坐牢
No jail.
加拉格女士  你明白
Ms. Gallagher, I want to make sure
现在的情况吗
you understand what's happening.
只要你认罪  你会成为一名重罪犯
With this plea agreement, you will be a felon.
与此同时  你将被判缓刑三年
As such, you will serve three years probation,
在此期间  你不能离开伊利诺伊州
during which time you cannot leave the state of Illinois.
每周都要与你的假释官见一次面
You must meet with your probation officer once a week.
你将不能奉职于政府部门
You will not be able to get a government job,
担任公职  不能投票
hold public office, vote.
如果你持有护照  你必须将它上缴
If you possess a passport, you must surrender it.
你必须避免大量饮酒
You shall refrain from excessive use of alcohol.
你不能够购买或持有  使用  分销
You shall not purchase, possess, use, distribute,
给予任何违禁品
or administer any controlled substance.
你不应该与参与犯罪活动的人
You shall not engage with any persons involved
有任何来往
in criminal activity.
你将被软禁在家  等待后续通知
You will be under house arrest until further notice.
你明白我所说的一切吗
Do you understand what I'm saying?
明白  法官大人
Yes, your honor.
那么  你承认自己犯下藏毒罪
Then how do you plead to possession
以及危害儿童罪吗
and child endangerment?
我承认
I'm guilty.